Contact

- macieksitkowski.com
- github.com/sitek94
- msitkowski94@gmail.com
- +48 797 164 649
- Warsaw, Poland

Key skills

- React, Redux, JSX
- ✓ JavaScript, D3.js
- Responsive Web Design
- ✓ HTML5, CSS3

Additional skills

- ✓ Sass, CSS-in-JS
- ✓ Git, GitHub
- ✓ Jest, React Testing Library
- ✓ OAuth, Firebase
- ✓ TypeScript, Node.js

Languages

- Q Polish Native
- C English Fluent
- Q Spanish Communicative

Interests

- Playing chess
- Dancing bachata
- Learning new things
- Building habits
- Reading
- → Being active

MACIEK SITKOWSKI

Summary

Front-end developer that has 1 year of experience developing web applications and building websites. Broadens his knowledge by actively contributing to Open Source projects.

Projects

Habit Tracker App

React | React Query | React Router | Firebase | Material-UI

Habit Tracker is my final project for Harvard's CS50 course. It's built as MVP (minimal viable product) and its core functionality is to track user's habits.

Pocket Globe App

React | D3.js | TopoJSON | Material-UI

The app uses D3.js and React to create a highly interactive and responsive globe. It connects to various APIs to get data about selected country.

Work experience

Bartender/Waiter

Dolphin Bar & Restaurant, Mallorca, Spain

May 2018 - Oct 2019

Working in one of the busiest restaurants on the island I became a better team player. Additionally it was a great opportunity to learn Spanish and further improve my English.

Customer Service Assistant

Clothes2Order, Manchester, United Kingdom

Mar 2017 - May 2018

Being a part of Customer Service team and talking over the phone with clients from all around the world helped me improve both my communication and collaboration skills.

Production Operative

Marks & Spencer, Castle Donington, United Kingdom

Dec 2015 - Jan 2017

Working for the first time abroad and overcoming the challenges along the road taught me how to quickly adapt to new environments.

Certificates

CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science — Harvard University

Responsive Web Design Certification — freeCodeCamp

Algorithms and Data Structures Certification — freeCodeCamp

Data Visualization Certification — freeCodeCamp

Front End Libraries Certification — freeCodeCamp

Education

Warsaw University of Technology

Architecture and Urban Planning

Sep 2014 - Sep 2015